Daniel Esteves

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

Goal-oriented Web Developer with strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design software to develop customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of web design, user experience, usability and speed for multiple types of end-users. Successful at maintaining customer satisfaction through effective customer support.

Employment History

Frontend Web Developer, Cuyuní Sistemas, Caracas

JANUARY 2018 - JUNE 2018

Project coordination and web site creation

Web Developer, Netnovation, Caracas

JUNE 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Web site creation and network administration

Frontend Web Developer, Imkova, Caracas

JULY 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Freelance. Adaptive website layout from a base theme

Associate, Platzi, Bogotá

JANUARY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

We work to deliver perfect courses to your hands

JavaScript Fullstack Developer, Seeed Us, Coral Gables

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Working as a web developer for ecommerce sites

Education

Bachelor, U.E.P Pbro. Alfonso Cobos Lopez, Caracas

JULY 2011 - JULY 2016

TSU in Computing, IUTA, Caracas

FEBRUARY 2017 - JULY 2019

Details

Caracas

Venezuela

+584142205537

danestves@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Venezolano/a

DATE OF BIRTH

29/11/1998

Links

<u>Twitter</u>

YouTube

Website

Skills

CSS

JavaScript

React/NextJS/Gatsby

Vue/Nuxt

WordPress

NodeJS/Express

MongoDB/MySQL

Headless CMS

Languages

Spanish; Castilian

English